收下这个娃娃就是一个天大的错误
It was a big mistake acknowledging this doll.
一旦它到了你的手中
And through that,
无形的恶灵就迷惑了你的心智
the inhuman spirit tricked you.
是你允许它入侵你的生活
You gave it permission to infest your lives.
无形的恶灵是什么
What's an inhuman spirit?
那是一种不会以人形存在的东西
It's something that's never walked the earth in human form.
那是一种邪恶的东西
It's something demonic.
那这个娃娃没有被附身吗
So, the doll was never possessed?
是的 这个娃娃只是一个媒介
No, it was used as a conduit.
它几经易手 让人误以为是她被附身了
It was moved around to give the impression of possession.
恶灵不会附身在东西上
Demonic spirits don't possess things.
只会附身在人身上
They possess people.
它想要占据你的心
It wanted to get inside of you.
基于这种特殊的情况
And given this unusual feature,
这个娃娃需要进行妥善的存放
the doll will need to be properly cared for.
妥善
Cared for?
这娃娃就该被毁掉
It should be destroyed.
那只会让事态恶化
That would only make things worse.
我们觉得最好还是由我们带走这个娃娃
We think it best the doll come with us.
我们会把它放在安全的地方
We'll keep it somewhere safe.
听起来是个不错的主意
That sounds like a great idea.
她是你们的了
She's all yours.
∮ 我的梦 ∮
∮ The dreams I hold ∮
∮ 是金色的 ∮
∮ Is a band of gold ∮
∮ 而爱留下的 ∮
∮ And the memories ∮
∮ 这些记忆 ∮
∮ Of what love could be ∮
你觉得还有多久能到
How much longer, do you think?
大概还有一小时
About an hour.
你还是把座椅放下来休息一下吧
Why don't you put your head back? Get some rest.
不行 你从超市回家都能迷路
No, you get lost coming home from the supermarket.
我要是睡着的话 醒来我们就在加州了
If I do that, we might end up in California.
那你醒来就能听到太平洋的声音了
Well, so you wake up to the sound of the Pacific.
那有什么不好的
Nothing wrong with that.
我还能顺路接上朱蒂
I'll pick up Judy on the way.
听起来很棒 爱德
Ah, that actually sounds so nice, Ed.
我们应该好好计划一下
We should plan on it.
怎么回事
What's this?
你们得掉头 前头发生了很严重的交通事故
You folks need to turn around. Pretty bad accident up ahead.
我们能帮什么忙吗
Uh, anything we can do?
你是医生什么的吗
You a doctor or something?
是什么的吧
Or something.
- 他只是想说我们很乐意帮忙 - 好吧
- He just meant if you need an extra set of hands. - Yeah.
我们能搞定 谢了
We got it covered. Thanks.
娃娃不错
Nice doll.
看起来不错而已
That's what you think.
你们得回到三英里前的那个出口
All right, you're gonna head three miles back to the last exit.
你们转26号路
You'll hop on 26,
可以绕道
that'll loop you around.
- 26号路 明白了 - 谢谢 警官
- 26. Got it. - Thank you, Officer.
只是一个路人和他的娃娃
A guy and his doll.
我觉得我们开过头了
I think we missed our turn.
没有 布里奇沃特路就在前面
We didn't miss it. Bridgewater's just up ahead.
什么布里奇沃特路 我们要去老布里奇路
Bridgewater? Old Ridge Road.
你怎么会觉得是布里奇沃特路
Where did you get Bridgewater from?
好吧 我觉得我们是开过头了
Well, you know what? I think we missed our turn.
我会留心找太平洋的
I'll keep my eye out for the Pacific.
爱德
Ed?
- 爱德 - 别急 别急
- Ed? - Hang on, hang on.
- 拜托 - 发生了什么
- Come on. - What just happened?
我打开前盖看看
I'll pop the hood and find out.
小心点
Well, be careful.
好了
There we go.
(玛丽威尔公墓)
我喜欢你的娃娃
I like your doll.
我觉得好冷
I feel cold.
你刚遭遇了一场交通意外
You were just in an accident.
是吗
I was?
抱歉
Sorry.
搭错线了
Wires crossed.
(玛丽威尔公墓)
这样应该好了
That should do it.
亲爱的 你没事吧
Honey, you okay?
爱德
Ed!
我没事
I'm okay.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry!
我的车好像突然着了魔
All of a sudden it was like somebody took over my truck.
我控制不了 你没事吧
I had no control. Are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
是那个娃娃 爱德
It's the doll, Ed.
它是召唤其他灵体的灯塔
It's a beacon for other spirits.
这边
Over here.
- 神父 越快越好 - 是吗
- Father, sooner the better. - Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
不要自作聪明
Be not wise in thine own eyes.
敬畏耶和华 远离恶事
Fear the Lord and depart from evil.
耶和华咒诅恶人的家庭
The curse of the Lord is in the house of the wicked.
赐福与义人的居所
But He blesseth the habitation of the just.
他讥诮那好讥诮的人
Surely, He scorneth the scorners,
赐恩给谦卑的人
but He giveth grace unto the lowly.
智慧人必承受尊荣
The wise shall inherit the glory,
愚昧人高升也成为羞辱
but shame shall be the promotion of fools.
阿门
Amen.
我们还需要一层防护屏障
We need another barrier of protection.
圣洁的屏障
A holy one.
我同意
I agree.
祈祷的效果有限
The blessing will only do so much.
三一教堂
That chapel glass
被毁前的教堂玻璃
we got from Trinity Church before it was torn down,
在哪里
where is that?
"原谅他人
"Let us forgive those
对我们的侵犯
who trespass against us
并使我们不受
and lead us not into temptation,
邪恶的诱惑"
but deliver us from evil."
阿门
Amen.
有用吗
Did it work?
邪恶被压抑了
The evil is contained.
沃伦收藏室是全世界最大的收藏遭到鬼魂影响和诅咒物件的收藏室
由于其藏有及极其邪恶的力量
沃伦夫妇每周会该收藏室进行祈祷赐福
收藏室中的每件物品都有其独一无二的恐怖来历
但是沃伦夫妇认为其中有一件物品蕴含的邪恶力量远甚于其他...
《安娜贝尔3: 回家》
(一年后)
(英雄还是骗子 争议驱魔引发热议)
好了 朱蒂
Okay, Judy.
我看到玛丽·艾伦的车停着了 去拿好你的东西
I just saw Mary Ellen pull up. Go and get your things.
但是先把你的麦片放...
But first put your cereal in the...
好吧 算了
All right. Never mind.
我来吧
I'll do it.
(英雄还是骗子 争议驱魔引发热议)
那是什么
What's that?
你是我的英雄
Well, you're my hero.
订披萨的钱放在柜子上了
The pizza money is on the counter
号码就在电话机边
and numbers are by the phone.
完美
Perfect.
我们明天一大早就会回来
And we'll be back early tomorrow morning.
你们不用着急 我们没事的
Well, and take your time, we'll be fine.
- 对吧 朱蒂 - 嗯
- Right, Judy? - Yeah.
- 那你会... - 乖乖的
- So, you'll... - Behave? Yes.
而且你会记得
And you'll remember to go to...
记得准时上床睡觉
Remember to go to bed on time.
绝对的
Absolutely.
- 好吧 别忘了... - 好好玩
- All right, don't forget to... - To have fun.
- 我知道 - 也对
- I know. - That, too.
你们是排练好的吗
Did you guys rehearse that, or what?
(圣托马斯 天主教学校)
地球呼叫朱蒂
Earth to Judy!
怎么了
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
我没事
I'm fine.
还有几个小时就到周末了
Well, it's just a couple more hours until the weekend.
我要趁有空赶紧去超市买点吃用
I'm gonna run to the market for supplies during my free period.
然后我就来接你 好吗
I'll pick you up after, okay?
听起来很棒
Sounds super.
再见 朱蒂
Bye, Judy!
过得愉快
Have a good day!
法雷太太 就在这边
Mrs. Faley, it's right over here.
我带你去
Let me show you.
(英雄还是骗子 争议驱魔引发热议)
你怎么能不告诉我 沃伦夫妇到底是干什么的
How could you not tell me what the Warrens did for a living?
你现在不是应该在上数学课吗
Shouldn't you be in math class?
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen!
我当初给史密斯夫妇当了两年保姆
I babysat the Smiths for over two years
也没告诉过你他们是干什么的
and never told you what they did.
那他们是干什么的
Oh, what do they do?
他们是足疗师
They're podiatrists.
这完全不一样
So not the same.
好吧 我等下肯定要来找你
Well, obviously, I'm coming over later.
我们要一起完成一个
We do have that social studies project
社会调研
that we need to work on.
我们没有什么调研
We don't have any project.
但是他们怎么会知道
Okay, but how would they know?
她可会通灵
She's psychic.
那他们就是英雄
Then, they're heroes.
我觉得他们只是
I think they're concerned parents
不希望自己的孩子受到负面影响的
who wouldn't want negative influences
一对操心的父母
around their child.
什么负面影响
What negative influence?
就因为我有时候会过了宵禁时间才回家吗
'Cause I sometimes stay out past curfew?
不止如此
Among other things.
那房子里是什么样的
So, what's it like inside the house?
都是恐怖的音乐和蜘蛛网吗
Is it all creepy music and cobwebs?
不 不 就是乏味的郊区房子
No. No, it's boring suburbia.
连你的储物柜都比那里恐怖点
The inside of your locker is scarier.
等等 谁要开派对 怎么没邀请我
Wait. Whose party, and why wasn't I invited?
朱蒂的生日快到了
Judy's birthday is coming up,
所以我们要提前庆祝
so we're gonna celebrate early.
你真的是最棒的保姆
You really are the best babysitter, you know that?
拍马屁也没用
Compliments will get you nowhere.
那威胁呢
What about threats?
你有没有注意到谁在收银呢
Did you, uh, happen to notice who's working checkout?
- 非常感谢 - 再见
- Thank you so much. - See you soon.
你不会这么做的
You wouldn't.
你知道他们都管他叫什么吧
You know what they call him, right?
什么
What?
大胆鲍勃
Bob's- Got- Balls.
你好吗
How you doing?
你好 丹妮拉
Hi, Daniela.
你好 玛丽·艾伦
Hi, Mary Ellen.
就这些了吗
Is this everything?
- 我想是的 - 好
- I think so. - Oh, cool.
你住在沃伦家附近吧 鲍勃
You live near the Warrens, don't you, Bob?
嗯 玛丽·艾伦今晚要去他们家做保姆
Yeah, Mary Ellen's babysitting for them tonight.
嗯 我就住在他们家对面那条街
Yeah. Yeah, I live right across the street.
你有没有注意到他们家有什么恐怖的地方
Do you ever see anything scary over there?
有没有什么鬼魂
Like a ghost, maybe?
鲍勃
Bob...
法雷太太在五号货架
Mrs. Faley went ahead and dropped
弄撒了一罐番茄酱
a can of tomato sauce in aisle five,
那看上去就像是犯罪现场 去拿拖把
and it looks like a crime scene, so get the mop.
女士们 你们还好吗
Ladies. Did you find everything okay?
很好 先生
Yes, sir.
鲍勃没给你们惹什么麻烦把
Bob here is not giving you any trouble, is he?
- 没有 - 没有
- No. - No.
- 交给我吧 谢谢 爸爸 - 好吧
- Yeah, I got it. Thanks, Dad. - All right.
我马上就去
I'll do it right after.
好了 你都看到了什么
So, what'd you see?
在沃伦家
At the Warrens'?
没什么 没什么
Uh, nothing. Nothing.
一共3.5美元 那么...
Um, your total is $3.50, so...
但是你早就知道沃伦夫妇是干什么的吧
But you knew what the Warrens did?
是有一些传言 但是...
There were rumors, I guess, but...
传言 有意思
Rumors. Interesting.
你知道也有关于你的传言吗 鲍勃
Did you know there's a rumor going around about you, Bob?
等等 真的吗 什么传言
Wait, really? What is it about?
是关于一个女孩...
Uh, it's about a girl who has a...
好吧 你可以来 住口
Fine. You can come. Stop.
- 抱歉 - 抱歉
- Sorry. - Sorry.
- 都是我不好 - 没关系
- That's totally my fault. - It's okay.
那...
So, what...
再见 鲍勃 谢谢
Bye, Bob. Thanks.
再见
Bye.
她忘了拿她的蛋
Uh, she forgot her eggs, so...
给我
Here.
她喜欢你
She likes you.
那是个意外
There's been an accident.
别碰她
Don't touch her.
你会被服身的
You'll get obsessed.
- 是附身 - 我说的就是附身
- It's "possessed." - That's what I said.
既然你懂这么多
Anyways, if you know so much,
你不如告诉我们 你能不能抓到鬼身上的虱子
why don't you tell us if you can catch cooties from a ghost?
你抓不到的
You can't.
那你怎么抓呢
Well, then how'd you get 'em?
安东尼·莱欧斯
Anthony Rios!
别逼我把你姐姐叫过来
Don't make me get your sister.
拜托不要
Please don't.
那就走开 你们都走开 快点
Then go. All of you. Come on.
我们走
Come on. Let's go!
很抱歉 我去不了你的生日派对了 朱蒂
I'm sorry I can't come to your birthday party, Judy.
你也来不了了吗
You can't either?
我父母说我还没有做好 面对死亡的准备
My parents said I'm not really prepared to process death yet.
这是生日派对
It's a birthday party.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你收到这种待遇多久了
Hey, how long has that been happening?
自从大家这周都知道那篇文章的事以后
Since everyone heard about the article this week.
- 求你不要告诉我父母 - 我不会的
- Please don't tell my parents. - I won't.
只要你不让我说
I won't as long as you do.
- 我不希望他们担心 - 他们是父母
- I don't want them to worry. - They're parents.
不管需不需要担心
They're worried about everything
他们都会担心的
whether they need to be or not.
(纪念迈克尔·莫里塞神父)
你确定你现在的烦心事
Are you sure the bullying is
只有受同学欺负吗
the only thing that's bothering you?
那不是烦心事
That isn't bothering me.
你懂我的意思
You know what I mean.
记得我们说好的
And remember our deal.
没有秘密
No secrets.
我知道
I know.
我没有秘密
I don't have any.
你去超市买了什么
What did you get at the store?
惊喜
A surprise.
- 你说没有秘密的 - 惊喜不是秘密
- You said no secrets. - A surprise isn't a secret.
- 那是什么 - 是惊喜
- What is it then? - It's a surprise.
你会弄得一团糟的
You're gonna make a mess.
给蛋糕留点
Save some for the cake.
不
No.
我觉得有人在敲门
I think there's someone at the door.
我敲了十分钟的门
I was knocking on the door for, like, ten minutes.
你怎么进来的
How did you even get in?
后门
Back door.
这是灵铃吗
Is this a spirit bell?
什么是灵铃
What's a spirit bell?
那会告诉你你身边有没有灵体
It tells you if you're in the presence of any spirits.
- 那的确是咯 - 不是
- So, it is one. - No.
这只是一个铃铛 我妈妈喜欢收集
It's just a bell. My mom collects them.
你是谁
Who are you?
她是丹妮拉 她吃完蛋糕就走
She's Daniela, and she leaves after cake.
太好了
Oh, good!
我爱蛋糕
I love cake.
那么 朱蒂
So, Judy.
你爸妈会不会留着些什么恐怖的东西
Don't your parents, like, keep any creepy stuff around?
没有
No.
他们把那些东西都锁在一个房间里
They keep it all locked away in a room.
那我们至少能进去看看吗
Well, can we at least go in and look?
不行
No!
那个房间不该进去
It's not really good for anyone to go in there.
为什么
How come?
就是不应该
Just isn't.
等等
Wait.
来
Here.
生日礼物
Birthday present.
是什么
What is it?
你看看
Look inside.
你哪来的钱买的
How did you even afford those?
那是我自己旧的那双
They're my old ones.
但是我只用过一次
But I only ever used them once
因为我第一次穿上就摔断了胳膊
'cause I broke my arm the first time I put them on.
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
她看上去协调性比我好多了
She looks way more coordinated.
这会划坏地板的
They're gonna ruin the floors.
那我们能去街上玩吗
Can we go around the block, then?
- 我觉得不该... - 好主意
- I don't think... - Good idea.
你们去吧
You guys go.
我会盯着蛋糕 确保不会烤糊
I'll watch the cake and make sure it doesn't burn.
好吧 但是不要随意乱逛 不要乱碰东西
Fine. But don't snoop. Don't touch.
什么都别做 拜托
Don't do anything. Please?
待在厨房里 你保证
Stay in the kitchen. Promise me.
我保证
I promise.
(沃伦夫妇恶魔巫术事物咨询所)
(危险 请勿触碰任何东西)
不管了
Fuck it.
我请求另一边的鬼魂
I am calling out to the spirits on the other side.
请打开这扇门 让我进去
Please unlock this door and let me in.
该死
Shit.
请不要批判我
Please don't judge me.
阿门
Amen.
(黑皮)
(触觉配对)
你怎么会被关在这里面呢
What'd you do to get in there?
如果这个房间里面有鬼魂
If there is a presence here in this room,
请给我一个征兆
please give me a sign.
任何征兆都行
Any sign at all.
爸爸
Dad?
这太愚蠢了
This is stupid.
(警告 绝对 不要 打开)
该死
Shit.
你把蛋糕烤糊了 丹妮拉
You burnt the cake? Daniela.
只有上面
Only the top.
放点糖霜上去就好
Just put frosting on it.
她不会知道的
She'll never know.
轮滑鞋玩得怎么样
How'd it go with the skates?
她很喜欢 直到她在回来的路上摔了一跤
She loved them until she fell on the way back
蹭破了膝盖
and skinned her knee.
总比摔断了手好
Better than breaking her arm.
她现在在哪里呢
Where is she anyway?
她在外面喂鸡
She's out feeding the chickens.
他们还养了鸡吗
They have chickens?
你的膝盖怎么样了
How's your knee?
看起来至少你的牛仔裤需要缝几针了
Looks like your jeans will at least need some stitches.
没事的
It's okay.
总会有意外
Accidents happen.
你已经害怕了吗
So, are you scared yet?
害怕 什么 没有
Scared? What? No.
谁说他们害怕了
Who says they're scared?
我班上的同学
Kids in my class.
安东尼·莱欧斯先开始的
Anthony Rios started it.
我恨他
I hate him.
等等 托尼·莱欧斯开始的吗
Wait. Tony Rios started it?
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
是啊 他是我弟弟
Yeah, he's my brother.
安东尼·莱欧斯是你的弟弟吗
Anthony Rios is your brother?
我懂 别把他和我相提并论
Yeah, I know. Don't hold it against me.
我也不喜欢他
I don't like him either.
你知道 他现在还尿床
You know, he still wets the bed.
可别说是我说的
You didn't hear it from me.
你也可以说 我不在乎
Or maybe you did, I don't care.
但还是...
Still, just...
别太为难他
go a little easy on him.
今年发生了很多事
It's been a tough year.
你失去了某个人 是吗
You lost somebody, didn't you?
我爸爸...
My dad. Uh...
玛丽·艾伦和你说的吗
Did Mary Ellen tell you?
不是
No.
我就是知道
I just knew.
外送
Um, for delivery.
我想点个大号的
Could I do one large, please?
是维曼街3506号
Um, it's gonna be 3506 Wayman Street.
太好了 谢谢
Oh, perfect. Thank you.
来了
Coming.
别着急啊
Hold your horses.
谁啊
Who is it?
有人吗
Hello?
丹妮拉
Daniela?
安娜贝尔在吗
Is Annabelle there?
谁
Who?
安娜贝尔能出来玩吗
Can Annabelle come out to play?
我觉得你走错了
I think you have the wrong house.
这里没有叫安娜贝尔的
There's no Annabelle here.
她在呢
Yes, she is.
她就在你后面
She's right behind you.
人们总是...他们对死亡的态度好奇怪
People are just... They're really weird about death.
也许学校里的孩子正是因此才找你麻烦的
That's probably why the kids pick on you at school.
他们很害怕
It scares them.
他们把死亡看做一种谁都不想沾染的疾病
They treat it like it's some disease they don't wanna get,
即便其实人人都有这种病
even though everyone already has it.
但其实是这样的
But here's the thing.
我以前都认为死了就是一命呜呼了
I used to think it was fatal and whammo.
就像是没了
It's, like, out.
就像关掉了电视
Like turning off a TV.
然后我知道了你父母的事
Then I learned about your parents
还有他们对死后之事 这类东西的探索...
and their whole exploration into the afterlife and stuff...
他们给了我希望
and they gave me hope.
也许生命还是会继续的
That maybe life goes on somehow.
也许
Maybe...
我亲爱的爸爸还在某处
my darling dad is still out there somewhere.
"亲爱的爸爸"
"Darling dad"?
这是我们之间的称呼
It was a thing.
他是亲爱的爸爸 我是亲爱的丹妮拉
He was darling dad, and I was darling Daniela...
很蠢
Stupid.
他还在某个地方的
He's still out there, you know.
你这么认为吗
You think so?
我爸爸妈妈也会说他在的
My parents would say he is, too.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我马上回来
Be right back.
爸爸
Dad?
丹妮拉
Daniela?
Daniela!
她去哪里了
Where did she go?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
丹妮拉 你不能下去的
Daniela, you're not supposed to go down there!
- 你在干什么 - 我以为我看到了什么
- What are you doing? - I thought I saw something.
你看到了什么
What did you see?
算了 不重要
Forget it. It doesn't matter.
(想我吗)
朱蒂
Judy?
耶和华啊 我信任你
In thee, O Lord, do I put my trust.
你凭你的公义
Let me never be put to confusion.
搭救我
Deliver me into Thy righteousness
救拔我 侧耳听...
and cause me to escape. Incline Thine ear...
朱蒂 朱蒂
Hey! Hey, Judy! Judy.
怎么回事 怎么了
What's going on? What's wrong?
怎么回事
What's going on?
出什么事了
What happened?
没什么
Nothing.
朱蒂
Judy...
我就是害怕
I just got scared.
害怕什么
Scared of what?
有时候
Sometimes...
我会看到一些东西
I see things.
就像我妈妈会看到一些东西一样
Like how my mom sees things.
你是说鬼魂之类的吗
You mean like ghosts?
你是在哪里看到它们的
Where do you see them?
我去哪儿都能看到
Everywhere I go.
朱蒂
Judy...
鬼魂也曾经是人
Ghosts used to be people.
你遇到的每个人都不一定是坏人 所以
And not every person you meet is bad... so
也许不一定每个鬼魂都是坏的
maybe not all ghosts are bad, either.
丹妮拉
Daniela.
- 你得来看看这个 - 什么
- You have to see this. - What?
这是沃伦夫妇以前接手的一次调查
It's this case the Warrens investigated about this girl
关于一个被摆渡人吓到的女孩
who was terrorized by something called the Ferryman.
这是他杀死的那个女孩的照片
Here's a picture of the girl he killed.
看上去眼熟吗
Look familiar?
你们俩很可能是姐妹呢
I mean, you two could be sisters.
如果你有兴趣的话 这是剩余的档案
Here's the rest of the file, if you want to take a look.
看看这些东西
Look at all this stuff.
真厉害
How cool.
这是黑皮的档案
Okay, this is the file on the Black Shuck.
黑皮
The Black Shuck?
这是沃伦夫妇曾今去英格兰
It was a case the Warrens investigated
调查一个人被一只猎犬附身的事
about a hellhound that possessed a man in England.
整个镇子都被他吓坏了
He terrorized the shit out of this town.
(可能是猎犬 迷雾 圣玛丽教堂 公墓)
他们眼睛上的硬币是怎么回事
What's with the coins over their eyes?
什么
What?
我不知道 我没有了解得这么深
Oh, I don't know. I didn't get that far.
人们以前都会在死人眼睛上放硬币
They used to put them over the eyes of the dead
好让摆渡人
to pay the Ferryman,
带他的灵魂前往阴间
so he could take their souls to the underworld.
这是他的摆渡费
It was his toll.
我们该离开这里了
Okay, we should go.
没关系 我有时候也喜欢偷溜进来
It's okay. I sometimes like to snoop, too.
你知道这是干什么的吗 朱蒂
Do you know what this does, Judy?
我觉得这应该是吊唁者手镯
I think it's called a Mourner's Bracelet.
这能让你联系你过世的爱着的人
It helps you contact your lost loved ones.
那是什么
What's that?
这是我爸爸妈妈最近在调查的事
It's a case my parents investigated recently.
这件婚纱
The wedding dress.
会缠上人
It haunts people.
会让人变得很暴力
And it makes them violent.
那这件婚纱现在在哪里
Where is the dress now?
在走廊尽头的收藏室里
Down the hall in the artifact room.
我是说 这种东西都在那房间里
I mean, that's where all this stuff is.
对吧 朱蒂
Right, Judy?
你之前就是这么说的
That's what you said earlier.
嗯
Yeah.
我爸爸说你那里面的所有东西
My dad says that everything in there
不是遭到鬼魂影响 就是被诅咒了
is either haunted, cursed,
或者用在某种仪式中
or used in some ritualistic practice.
那里面的那个娃娃呢
What about the doll that's in there?
因为我看过你爸爸的一篇采访
Because I read this interview with your dad...
不
No.
不要提她
Don't talk about her.
为什么
Why not?
她被关起来是有原因的
She's in a case for a reason.
好吧 我们该离开这里
Okay, we should go.
我想看看这里有什么
I wonder what's on this.
不 丹妮拉 等等
No, Daniela! Wait!
我命令你 不洁的灵魂
I command you, unclean spirit,
和你的仆从一起
along with all your minions...
我命令你
I command you
听从我的每一个字
to obey me to the letter!
好了 别闹了
Okay, show's over.
我们去找点别的事做
Let's go do something else.
找点合适的事
Do something that's actually appropriate.
拜托
Come on,
你至少想听听那武士装的故事吧
don't you at least wanna hear about the samurai?
这个呢
What about this one?
我不记得我玩过这个了
I don't remember that one.
怎么玩的
How do you play?
试试看就知道了
Let's find out.
好吧 你要抽一张卡片
Okay. Okay, so you draw a card
你要通过你的触觉
and whatever picture it has on it
在盒子里找到
is the object you try to find
你卡片上的东西
by feeling around inside the box.
如果你抽出来的东西就是卡片上的东西
If the object you pull out matches the picture,
那你就能得一分
then you get a point.
你先来
You go first.
好吧
Okay.
你要去应门吗
You gonna get that?
嗯
Yeah.
抱歉 你们继续玩
Sorry, you guys keep playing.
得一分
Oh, got a point.
不错
Nice.
谁啊
Hello?
你好 玛丽·艾伦
Hi, Mary Ellen.
你好
Hi.
你记不记得在超市里
Remember how, at the store,
丹妮拉说你会来这里做保姆吗
Daniela said that you were babysitting here?
嗯
Yeah. Yeah.
我也记得
Me, too.
不管怎么样 所以我才过来的
Anyways, that's why I'm here.
鲍勃 他们不希望我带男孩来
Bob, they don't really want me having boys over.
不 我不是这个意思 我不想进去
No, that's not what I meant. I don't wanna come in.
我只是...
I just, uh...
我是说 我也想 但是
I mean, I would, but...
那个...
Well...
我只是知道你会在这里
I just knew you were gonna be here,
我只是想过来和你说说话
and I just wanted to come by and talk to you
没有我那笨蛋老爹或者其他人来打扰
without my stupid dad or somebody interrupting.
大胆鲍勃
Bob's- Got- Balls!
不错啊
Nice.
你们俩要一起吃披萨吗
You two sharing some pizza?
我去拿钱
I should get the money.
你们俩是...
Are you two, like...
我...我也想呢
I... I wish.
你知道你得唬唬她吧
You know you need to, like, woo her, right?
唬唬她
Woo her?
玛丽·艾伦这样的家伙得唬唬
Yeah. Guys like Mary Ellen, they need to be wooed.
你是说玛丽·艾伦这样的女孩吗
You mean girls like Mary Ellen.
我刚刚说了什么
What did I say?
家伙
Guys.
那我要怎么唬唬她
So, how do I woo her?
唬唬只有一个办法
There's only one way to woo.
很明显
It's obvious.
摇滚
Rock and roll.
给 不用找了
Here. Keep it.
太好了
Sweet.
谢谢 那也就是说这个可以给你了
Thanks, and that means you can keep this.
少一片
Minus one slice.
我在车里吃了
I enjoyed that in the car.
回头见 大胆
See you later, Balls.
我也想邀请你进来 但是我也说了...
I would invite you in, but like I said...
不 没关系
No, yeah, it's cool.
我想着只是来打个招呼 所以...
I thought I'd just stop by and say hi, I guess, so...
我见到你很高兴
I'm glad you did.
我也是
Me, too.
鲍勃
Hey, Bob, um...
他们为什么要这么叫你
How come they call you that?
你知道我是篮球队的
Well, you know how I'm the equipments manager
设备管理员吧
for the basketball team?
- 嗯 - 这就是原因
- Yeah. - That's why.
其实没有什么背后的故事什么的
There's not really, like, a story or anything behind it.
就是"喂 我要球"
Just like, "Hey, I need balls."
我就说
I'm, like,
"球来了 接着"
"I got it. Balls. Got 'em."
唬头见
I'll see woo later.
我是说 回头见
You. You. I'll see you later.
我先走了
I'm gonna go.
再见 鲍勃
Bye, Bob.
再见
Bye.
好了 卡洛琳
All right, Carolyn,
连灵媒都不可能预言到
even a fortune teller couldn't have predicted
我们为你和唐选择的约会对象
the place we picked for your date with Don.
因为谁能想到
Because who could ever have dreamed up a place
像内华达州的拉斯维加斯
as unbelievably fabulus as
这么棒的地方
Las Vegas, Nevada?
没错 就是这么棒
Yes, "amazing" is the word for it.
你们将一路飞到
You'll be flying off for a fling
拉斯维加斯的市中心
at the fabulous town of Las Vegas,
在弗朗明哥大酒店下榻
to be guests of the fantastic Flamingo Hotel,
那可是拉斯维加斯大道最受欢迎的地方
a favorite spot along the Vegas Strip.
道恩 我们还为你准备了特殊的礼物
And, Dawn, as a little special gift for you...
你能把手伸过来吗
Can you get your arms around there?
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen?
丹妮拉
Daniela?
∮ 祝你生日快乐 ∮
∮ Happy birthday to you ∮
∮ 祝你生日快乐 亲爱的朱蒂 ∮
∮ Happy birthday, dear Judy ∮
∮ 祝你生日快乐 ∮
∮ Happy birthday to you ∮
好了 朱蒂
Okay, Judy.
准备好上床睡觉了吗
Ready for bed?
这是给你的
This is for you.
这是什么
What's this?
(你被邀请啦)
这是我生日派对的邀请函
It's an invitation to my birthday party.
我觉得不会有多少人来
I don't think many people are gonna come...
但你会来吗
but will you?
看看我拿到了什么
You see what I got?
我几周前就拿到了
I got mine weeks ago.
那你会来吧
So, you'll come?
我绝对不会错过的
I wouldn't miss it.
∮ 你保护我不被伤害 ∮
∮ You sheltered me from harm ∮
∮ 你让我温暖 ∮
∮ You kept me warm ∮
什么声音
What's that?
∮ 你让我温暖 ∮
∮ You kept me warm ∮
天啊
Oh, my God.
不是吧
It isn't.
真的是
It is.
∮ 你保护我不被伤害 ∮
∮ You sheltered me from harm ∮
∮ 你让我温暖 ∮
∮ You kept me warm ∮
∮ 你让我 ∮
∮ You kept me ∮
∮ 温暖 ∮
∮ warm ∮
- 鲍勃 - ∮ 你让我的生命 ∮
- Bob! - ∮ You gave my life... ∮
∮ 没有人会知道 ∮
∮ Nobody else will ever know ∮
∮ 我无法放弃的内心 ∮
∮ The part of me That can't let go ∮
∮ 我愿意放弃我的一切 ∮
∮ I would give anything I own ∮
鲍勃胆子真大
Bob's got balls.
∮ 只为让你回到身边 ∮
∮ Just to have you back again ∮
我看上去怎么样 我的吸入器呢
How do I look? Where's my inhaler?
该死 不 在我车里 我该怎么办
Shit, no, it's in my car. What am I supposed to do?
你没事的
You will be fine.
只是鲍勃而已
It's only Bob.
∮ 只为再次触碰你 ∮
∮ Just to touch you once again ∮
该死
Shit!
操
Fuck!
该死
Shit!
不
No!
鲍勃
Bob?
他走了
He left.
希望他是回家练习去了
Hopefully he went home to practice.
好了 回床上去
Okay. Back up to bed.
丹妮拉
Daniela.
如果你能让我留下来 我能更安心
I'd feel better if you let me stay.
我可以早点起来 我们都不用告诉朱蒂
I can wake up early. We don't even have to tell Judy.
不 不 没关系
No. No, it's fine.
回家去吧
Go home.
但是
But...
什么但是
But what?
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
我觉得你让朱蒂好受多了
I actually think it helped Judy a lot.
很抱歉没让你看到什么蜘蛛网
Sorry you didn't get to see any cobwebs
或听到什么可怕的音乐
or hear any creepy music.
至少鲍勃那一出还是有点可怕的
Well, the Bob thing was kind of creepy, at least.
但是如果鲍勃半夜来敲门
But if Bob comes knocking on this door late at night,
你就放飞自我 让他进来吧
forget you're you for a minute and let him in.
明天给我打电话 分享细节
Call me tomorrow and tell me the details.
没什么好分享的细节
There will be no details to tell.
该死
Shit.
她的爸爸是怎么死的
How'd her dad die?
我觉得不该把这当做睡前故事来讲
I don't know if that's the best bedtime story.
你看看我爸妈是谁
Look who my parents are.
我早就习惯了
I'm used to it.
好吧
Well,
简短的版本就是 他死于车祸
the short of it is that he died in a car accident.
多说一两句就是...
And the long of it is that...
当时开车的人是丹妮拉
Daniela was driving.
是她的错吗
Was it her fault?
不是
No.
只有一个人
There's only one person
觉得是她的错
who actually thinks it was her fault.
好吧
Okay.
我们再来试试
Let's try this again.
如果这里有鬼...
If there is a presence here...
爸爸
Dad?
Dad.
是你害死我的
You did this to me!
都是你的错
It's all your fault!
回来
Get back here!
都是你害死我的
You did this to me!
(危险 请勿触碰任何东西)
不不不 拜托
No, no, no. Please.
拜托 不 别走 别走
Please, no, no. Don't go. Don't go.
不不不 过来
No, no, no. No, come here.
过来 过来 不 不
Come here, come here. No. No.
对不起
I'm sorry.
朱蒂
Judy?
他是这样把她从橱子里抓走的吗
Is that why he picked her up from the closet?
是的 肯定是这样的
Yes. That must have been it.
他会把她从橱里抓走 对吗
He's not gonna pick her up in a closet, is he?
你待在这里 不要出声
You stay here and don't make any noise.
怎么回事
What is happening?
我的咖啡呢
Where's my coffee?
早上好
Good morning.
你遇到了超自然...
You've been experiencing supernatural...
早上好 我的咖啡呢
Good morning. Where's my coffee?
等一下
Just a second.
他的眼睛上有银色的硬币
He had silver coins for his eyes.
她说他的光能指引你前往死亡之地
She said his light shows you the way to the land of the dead.
我只是想找到我的妹妹
I just wanna find my sister.
她第一次看到他是什么时候
And when did she first see him?
在他抓走她不久前
Not long before he took her.
她说她醒来 他就在她的房间
She said she'd wake up, and he'd be in her room...
看着她睡觉
watching her sleep.
她不见的那晚
The night she went missing,
我们都被一个声音吵醒了
we both woke up to a noise.
听上去像是硬币掉到地板上的声音
It sounded like a coin falling on the floor.
她要我在房间里等着
She told me to wait in her room.
我就等着她
So I did.
她再也没回来
She never came back.
我就去找她 结果走到了一个长长的走廊上
I went to look for her and ended up in a long hallway.
走廊里全是棺材
Filled with coffins.
昨晚
Last night...
我又被一个声音吵醒
I woke up to a noise.
又是一枚硬币落地的声音
Another coin being dropped.
他好像在
It was like he was...
他好像在召唤我
Like he was calling me.
你有没有见到过摆渡人
Have you ever seen the Ferryman?
你不付他摆渡费
If you don't pay his toll,
他就会夺走你的灵魂
he'll take your soul.
你不付他摆渡费 他就会夺走你的灵魂
If you don't pay his toll, he'll take your soul.
你不付他摆渡费
If you don't pay his toll,
他就会夺走你的灵魂
he'll take your soul.
你不付他摆渡费 他就会夺走你的灵魂
If you don't pay his toll, he'll take your soul.
该死 该死 不
Shit! Shit! Shit! No.
朱蒂 朱蒂
Judy! Judy!
朱蒂
Judy!
朱蒂 开门 朱蒂
Judy! Open the door, Judy!
我喜欢你的娃娃
I like your dolls.
朱蒂 朱蒂
Judy! Judy!
从后门出去
Go out the back!
我们被困住了
We're trapped.
- 喂 - 谢天谢地
- Hello? - Oh, thank God.
- 沃伦太太 - 妈妈
- Mrs. Warren? - Mom?
玛丽·艾伦 朱蒂
Mary Ellen? Judy?
一切都还好吗 没事吧
Is everything okay? What's going on?
朱蒂没事
Judy's fine.
你的房子里发生了一些奇怪的事
Something is happening inside your house
我觉得我们现在出去不安全
and I don't think it's safe to go outside.
我们不知道该怎么办
We're not really sure what to do.
能让我和安娜贝尔说说话吗
Can I speak to Annabelle?
什么
I'm sorry?
你要给她一个灵魂 亲爱的
You need to give her a soul, dear.
- 什么 - 一个灵魂 她要她的灵魂
- What? - A soul. She wants her soul.
给我她的灵魂
Give me her soul.
等等 不要
Wait! Don't!
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
(想我吗)
安娜贝尔
Annabelle.
那个娃娃 这一切都是她干的
The doll. She's the one who's doing all of this.
一个娃娃
A doll?
她想要一个灵魂
She wants a soul.
我只是想再见到他
I just wanted to see him again.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我想告诉他我很抱歉
I wanted to tell him I'm sorry.
我知道那就是我的错
I know it was my fault.
丹妮拉
Daniela...
你做了什么
what did you do?
我把她放了出来
I let her out.
你还碰了什么东西
What else did you touch?
所有东西
Everything.
快跑 快跑
Run! Run! Go!
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen!
是她的哮喘 她发作了
It's her asthma. She's having an attack.
吸入器在她的车里
The inhaler's in her car.
我去拿
I'll go get it.
不 我去
No! Let me!
朱蒂 快跑
Judy! Run!
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen!
给
Here.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
丹妮拉呢 她本来在你后面的
Where's Daniela? She came after you.
玛丽·艾伦 朱蒂
Mary Ellen? Judy?
- 我在这里 - 不
- I'm up here. - No.
那不是丹妮拉
That's not Daniela.
有东西控制住她了 我能感觉到
Something has a hold of her. I can feel it.
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
我们要找到安娜贝尔
We have to find Annabelle.
我们要把她放回到盒子里
We have to put her back in the case.
你知道她在哪里吗
Do you know where she is?
不知道
No.
等等 朱蒂 别去
Wait, wait, Judy, don't.
不是所有鬼都是坏的
Not all ghosts are bad.
对吧
Right?
不是所有鬼都是坏的
Not all ghosts are bad.
你说什么
What did you say?
我们走
Come on, let's go.
快点
Come on.
我去拿她
I'll get her.
不不不 停下
No, no, no. No! Just stop!
你父母把钥匙放在哪里
Where do your parents keep the key?
我不知道 这上面从来没锁
I don't know. It's never locked.
我知道钥匙在哪里
I know where the key is.
- 我来拿 - 不 不要
- I'll get it. - No! No, don't.
我来
I'll do it.
朱蒂
Judy!
我拿到了
I got it.
我们在天的父 愿你的名被尊为圣
Our Father, who art in heaven hallowed be Thy name.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我们日用的饮食 今日赐给我们
Give us this day our daily bread,
免我们的债
and forgive us for our trespasses
如同我们免了人的债
as we forgive those who trespassed against us.
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen?
快走
Go!
丹妮拉
Daniela.
丹妮拉 求你了
Daniela, please!
丹妮拉 住手
Daniela, stop!
住手
Stop!
我命令你 不洁的灵魂
I command you, unclean spirit,
和一同冒犯
along with all your minions,
上帝仆从的仆从
now attacking this servant of God.
- 我命令你听从我的每一个字 - 朱蒂 快跑
- I command you to obey me to the letter. - Judy, run!
以祂之名 他们将用祂之手
In his name, they will take up serpents...
铲除毒蛇 责罚邪恶
...with his hands and condemn all evil.
我命令你 不洁的灵魂
I command you, unclean spirit,
和你的仆从
along with all your minions,
- 听从我的每一个字 - 不 不
- To obey me to the letter. - No, no.
我 上帝的仆从
I, who am a servant of God...
我命令你 不洁的灵魂
I command you, unclean spirit,
和一同冒犯
along with all your minions,
上帝的仆从的仆从
now attacking this servant of God...
朱蒂
Judy!
朱蒂 朱蒂 朱蒂
Judy! Judy. Judy.
去拿娃娃
Get the doll!
- 关上门 - 我在努力
- Close it! - I'm trying!
快点
Hurry!
我们在天上的父 愿人都尊你的名为圣
Our Father who art in heaven, hallowed be Thy name.
愿你的国降临 愿你的旨意行在地上
Thy kingdom come, Thy will be done,
如同行在天上
on earth as it is in heaven.
把她放进去
Put her in!
我们日用的饮食 今日赐给我们
Give us this day our daily bread,
免我们的债
and forgive us for our trespasses,
如同我们免了人的债
as we forgive those who trespassed against us,
不叫我们遇见试探
lead us not into temptation,
救我们脱离凶恶
but deliver us from evil...
阿门
Amen.
结束了吗
Is it over?
邪恶已经被压抑了
The evil has been contained.
鲍勃
Bob?
- 你们还好吗 - 我们没事
- Are you guys okay? - Yeah. We're okay.
- 那你还好吗 - 不好
- Are you okay? - No!
外面有个狼人
There was a werewolf outside!
你看到了狼人
You saw the werewolf?
是的
Yeah.
他还救了我
He saved me from it.
真的吗
You did?
算是吧
Yeah. Kind of.
也许我们该去别的地方好好聊聊
Maybe we should talk about this somewhere else.
早上好 各位 康涅狄格州
Good morning from the staff of wpkw- pv6
哈特福德六台的观众
in Hartford, Connecticut.
这里是康涅狄格州的哈特福德 这里...
This is Hartford, Connecticut, the land of steady habits...
我爸妈
My parents.
该死 你们不该让男孩进来的
Shit! You're not supposed to have boys over.
我觉得这应该根本不是重点 鲍勃
I think that's the least of our concerns right now, Bob.
对 但我还是该走了
Yeah, yeah. I should probably still get going.
听着 快到返校节了
Hey, listen, um, so Homecoming is coming up
- 我想... - 好的 我愿意
- and I would really like... - Yes. I'll... I'll go.
和我一起吗
With me?
是的 如果沃伦夫妇没有先杀死我的话
Yes, if the Warrens don't kill me first.
我们把一切都告诉他们
We tell them everything.
妈妈
Mom!
朱蒂 你怎么这么早就起来了
Judy! What are you doing up so early?
别生气
Don't get mad...
你的车怎么了
What happened to your car?
来
Here we go.
我们享受自己的派对
We'll have our own party, huh?
- 怎么了 - 你至少能把那个东西拿下来吗
- What? - Can you please take that off?
不会一直这样的 我保证
It won't always be like this, I promise.
你迟早会找到
You know, and sooner or later,
理解你的人
you'll find people who understand.
至于那个小安东尼
And as for young Anthony,
他最好别让我逮到
he better hope I don't run into him anytime soon.
爱德
Ed.
生日快乐 朱蒂
Happy birthday, Judy.
谢谢
Thank you.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
我和我的弟弟聊了聊
I, uh, had a little talk with my brother.
谢谢
Thanks.
请进
Come in.
我男朋友能进来吗
Is it okay if my boyfriend joins?
当然了
Sure.
谢谢你们邀请我们
Hi, uh, thanks for having us.
大胆鲍勃
Bob's- Got- Balls.
真大胆
No kidding.
- 朱蒂 - 生日快乐 朱蒂
- Hi, Judy! - Happy birthday, Judy!
- 生日快乐 - 生日快乐
- Happy birthday! - Happy birthday!
- 你好 朱蒂 生日快乐 - 欢迎大家
- Hello, Judy, happy birthday. - Hey, guys, welcome.
一直有人来
Keep comin'.
生日快乐 朱蒂
Happy birthday, Judy.
- 安东尼 - 我真的很抱歉
- Anthony? - I'm really sorry.
我还能参加吗
Am I still invited?
当然了
Sure.
丹妮拉
Daniela?
我有东西给你
I have something for you.
给我吗
For me?
你发现这个房间里
You found out the hard way
有恶灵 也付出了惨痛的代价
that there is a lot of evil in this room.
但是你知道我为什么喜欢这里吗
But you know what I actually like about it?
这里的恶灵
All the evil in here...
都让我能够想起外界的美好
reminds me of all the good that's out there.
亲爱的丹妮拉
Darling Daniela.
是朱蒂和你说的吗
Did Judy tell you that?
不 是你爸爸说的
No. Your dad did.
他还告诉我 他很想你
He also tells me that he misses you.
不要再苛责你自己了
And to stop being so hard on yourself,
因为那并不是你的错
'cause it was not your fault.
谢谢你
Thank you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
你还年轻
You're young.
我在你这个年纪的时候
You know, when I was about your age,
曾经和我的一任男友在没告诉我父母的情况下
I once ran off with a boyfriend for three days
整整偷跑出去三天
without telling my parents.
我释放出了一个恶魔
I unleashed a demon.
所以这应该不是一码事
So not the same thing.
好吧 没错
Well, okay. True.
沃伦先生知道这一任男友吗
Does Mr. Warren know about this boyfriend?
他就是那个男友
He was the boyfriend.
有人想听歌吗
Anybody wanna hear a song?
好了
All right, okay.
[纪念洛琳·沃伦]